Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
If that's what love is
إذا كان هذا هو الحب
how utterly defenseless
كم هو عاجز تماما
and foolish it is.
وهذا أمر سخيف.
- I'm so sorry. - Wait...
- أنا آسف جدًا. - انتظر...
Geez, you have nothing to apologize for.
يا إلهي، ليس لديك ما تعتذر عنه.
Getting into this room.
الدخول إلى هذه الغرفة.
I'm just reminded of the mistake I made.
لقد ذكّرتني للتو بالخطأ الذي ارتكبته.
Whether it was right or wrong isn't for you to decide alone.
لا يمكنك أن تقرر وحدك ما إذا كان الأمر صحيحًا أم خطأ.
This is why I asked you to come.
لهذا السبب طلبت منك أن تأتي.
I kissed you here.
لقد قبلتك هنا.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
But I'm happy.
ولكنني سعيد.
Huh?
هاه؟
Because I've always wanted to do that.
لأنني أردت دائمًا أن أفعل ذلك.
Fumi.
يدخن.
Aren't you happy?
هل أنت غير سعيد؟
I...
أنا...
I've never thought about anything like that.
لم أفكر في شيء مثل هذا أبدًا.
I see.
أرى.
I thought that you...
اعتقدت أنك...
had feelings for me, too.
كان لديه مشاعر تجاهي أيضًا.
Well then...
حسنا إذن...
I'm sorry
أنا آسف
for all of this
لكل هذا
I do like you.
انا معجب بك.
Of course I do.
بالطبع أفعل.
You're beautiful
أنت جميلة
talented, and you work so hard.
موهوب، وأنت تعمل بجد.
You're one of a kind.
أنت فريد من نوعك.
There's no reason for me not to admire you.
ليس هناك سبب يمنعني من الإعجاب بك.
But that's exactly why.
ولكن هذا هو السبب بالضبط.
Kissing you like that...
قبلتك هكذا...
it shouldn't have happened.
كان لا ينبغي أن يحدث ذلك.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I'm dumped.
لقد تم التخلي عني.
I'm back.
لقد عدت.
Kaishin.
كاشين.
Mom said to dine together once a month from now on.
قالت أمي أننا سنتناول العشاء معًا مرة واحدة في الشهر من الآن فصاعدًا.
That's great.
هذا عظيم.
You'll have more time to talk with your family.
سيكون لديك مزيدًا من الوقت للتحدث مع عائلتك.
She also said she wants to meet my boyfriend.
وقالت أيضًا إنها تريد مقابلة صديقي.
Let's go together next time.
دعونا نذهب معًا في المرة القادمة.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
The bracelet I gave you the other day
السوار الذي أعطيتك إياه في اليوم الآخر
actually...
في الحقيقة...
it's part of a matching set.
إنه جزء من مجموعة متطابقة.
A heart?
قلب؟
A small, lonely heart
قلب صغير وحيد
but
لكن
when putting it together with your bracelet
عند وضعه مع سوارك
my heart
قلبي
is inside of yours.
هو بداخلك.
Ai-san.
أي-سان.
- I fall in... - Don't say it.
- لقد وقعت في... - لا تقل ذلك.
Don't tell me the rest.
لا تخبرني بالباقي.
Why not?
ولم لا؟
No.
لا.
I don't want to hear it.
لا أريد أن أسمع ذلك.
Wait, Ai-san.
انتظري، آيسان.
Ai-san!
مهلا، آي سان!
Ai-san.
أي-سان.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
I'm drafting a contract.
أنا أقوم بصياغة عقد.
What contract?
أي عقد؟
A new contract between us.
عقد جديد بيننا.
- We don't need a contract. - Yes, we do.
- لا نحتاج إلى عقد. - نعم نحتاج إليه.
- No, we don't.
- لا، لا نفعل ذلك. - نعم، نفعل ذلك.
No.
لا.
- Just listen to me. - No, Kaishin, you listen.
- فقط استمع لي. - لا، كايشين، استمع.
- Stop talking. - I love you.
- توقف عن الكلام. - أحبك.
From the bottom of my heart.
من أعماق قلبي.
I love you.
أحبك.
Why?
لماذا؟
Why did you say it?
لماذا قلت ذلك؟
Because I wanted to.
لأني أردت ذلك.
You know nothing.
أنت لا تعرف شيئا.
- Then tell me. - Gotta be quick...
- إذن أخبرني. - يجب أن تكون سريعًا...
This new contract.
هذا العقد الجديد.
Is 500,000 enough?
هل 500 ألف كافية؟
What?
ماذا؟
A million?
مليون؟
Or one and a half million?
أو مليون ونصف؟
If it's two million...
إذا كان مليونين...
that's probably too cheap for you.
ربما يكون هذا رخيصًا جدًا بالنسبة لك.
Stop it.
اوقفها.
It's enough.
هذا يكفي.
Two and a half million.
مليونين ونصف.
- Three million, three and a half... - I said stop it!
- ثلاثة ملايين، ثلاثة ونصف... - قلت توقف!
How much do I have to pay for your love?
كم يجب أن أدفع مقابل حبك؟
- What are you talking about? - I don't want any money.
- عن ماذا تتحدث؟ - لا أريد أي أموال.
Money isn't what I want.
المال ليس ما أريده.
I just want you.
انا فقط أريدك.
Let me love you.
دعينى أحبك.
I can't.
لا أستطبع.
I don't need love.
لا أحتاج إلى الحب.
You don't have to love me
ليس عليك أن تحبني
I don't want to get hurt.
لا أريد أن أتعرض للأذى.
Don't talk about love.
لا تتحدث عن الحب.
Get lost.
اغرب عن وجهي.
I don't need it.
لا أحتاجه.
I see.
أرى.
In that case.
في هذه الحالة.
I don't want it back.
لا أريده مرة أخرى.
My heart.
قلبي.
I don't want you to give it back.
لا أريدك أن تعيدها.
Let me just say one last thing.
دعني أقول شيئاً أخيراً.
I love you.
أحبك.
I don't love you.
أنا لا أحبك.
To truly fall in love with the ocean...
لكي تقع في حب المحيط حقًا...
I guess it wasn't meant to be.
أعتقد أنه لم يكن من المفترض أن يكون كذلك.
Ocean's Love: Where Love Returns (Episode 10)
حب المحيط: حيث يعود الحب (الحلقة 10)
Why is Himeka-san here too?
لماذا هيميكا سان هنا أيضًا؟
I invited her.
لقد دعوتها.
Why?
لماذا؟
I wanted to say goodbye to you both.
أردت أن أقول وداعا لكما.
I'm taking the boat tonight
سأستقل القارب الليلة
to go back to the island.
للعودة إلى الجزيرة.
Why so suddenly?
لماذا فجأة؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Then what about Teacher Ai?
إذن ماذا عن المعلم آي؟
You were the one who helped him grow.
لقد كنت الشخص الذي ساعده على النمو.
How can you just leave like this?
كيف يمكنك المغادرة هكذا؟
That's exactly why I asked you both to come.
هذا هو بالضبط السبب الذي جعلني أطلب منكما الحضور.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
Fumi-san and Himeka-san
فومي-سان وهيميكا-سان
you both know Ai-san very well.
كلاكما يعرف آي سان جيدًا.
But
لكن
in my perspective.
من وجهة نظري.
Ai-san is far more lonely
آي سان تشعر بالوحدة أكثر بكثير
yet still yearns for people connection.
ولا يزال يتوق إلى التواصل مع الناس.
So...
لذا...
please go see him more often.
من فضلك اذهب لرؤيته أكثر.
Even if he acts annoyed, please be patient with him.
حتى لو تصرف بإنزعاج، يرجى التحلي بالصبر معه.
If he asks for alcohol
إذا طلب الكحول
give him coffee.
أعطيه القهوة.
If he won't eat
إذا لم يأكل
take away all the coffee.
إزالة كل القهوة.
Then he'll eat.
ثم سوف يأكل.
Wait a minute.
انتظر دقيقة.
- But isn't that just... - Please take care of him...
- ولكن أليس هذا مجرد... - من فضلك اعتني به...
I'm counting on you.
أنا أعتمد عليك.
Are you really okay with this?
هل أنت بخير حقا مع هذا؟
What are you asking all of a sudden?
ماذا تسأل فجأة؟
About Kaishin.
حول كايشين.
Why didn't you stop him?
لماذا لم توقفه؟
Stop him?
أوقفه؟
Yeah, tell him not to go.
نعم، أخبره ألا يذهب.
"Stay by my side."
"ابقى بجانبي."
"Don't leave me." Something like that. Go after him!
لا تتركني. شيءٌ كهذا. الاحقه!
Why should I...
لماذا يجب علي...
Give me a break...
أعطني استراحة...
Don't give up
لا تستسلم
I'm already in agony.
أنا بالفعل في عذاب.
Do I really need to suffer any more?
هل أحتاج حقا إلى المعاناة أكثر؟
Love and pain...
الحب والألم...
They're supposed to be different.
من المفترض أن يكونوا مختلفين.
But the only love I've ever known
لكن الحب الوحيد الذي عرفته على الإطلاق
is synonymous with sorrow.
هو مرادف للحزن.
Gosh...
يا إلهي...
I told you, I can't write.
لقد قلت لك أنني لا أستطيع الكتابة.
No matter how I want to.
لا يهم كيف أريد ذلك.
When will it be finished? I want to know more than anyone.
متى سينتهي؟ أريد أن أعرف أكثر من أي شخص آخر.
Is that so?
هل هذا صحيح؟
What are you thinking about?
ماذا تفكر فيه؟
Huh?
هاه؟
Oh.
أوه.
Teacher Ai and Kaishin-san.
المعلم آي وكايشين سان.
When you think about it
عندما تفكر في الأمر
their story is like something out of a romance.
قصتهم تشبه إلى حد ما قصة رومانسية.
Two people who are polar opposites
شخصان متضادان تماما
meet and fall in love.
الالتقاء والوقوع في الحب.
Love...
حب...
Kaishin loves Teacher.
كايشين يحب المعلم.
And Teacher loves Kaishin.
والمعلم يحب كايشين.
For the first time, Teacher opened his heart to someone.
لأول مرة، فتح المعلم قلبه لأحد ما.
Is it really that easy?
هل الأمر سهل حقا إلى هذه الدرجة؟
For someone with a painful past
لشخص لديه ماضي مؤلم
who has always run from love
الذي هرب دائمًا من الحب
it's not easy to accept it.
ليس من السهل قبول ذلك.
Over here.
هنا.
About the other day
عن اليوم الآخر
- thank you so much. - You're welcome.
- شكرا جزيلا. - على الرحب والسعة.
Today.
اليوم.
I have something to tell you
عندي شيء أريد أن أخبرك به
I am thinking of treating you some cake to show my gratitude.
أنا أفكر في إهدائك بعض الكعكة لإظهار امتناني.
- Act cheeky again. - Then how about a reward cake for acing my test?
- تصرف بوقاحة مرة أخرى. - إذن ماذا عن كعكة مكافأة لتفوقي في الاختبار؟
Let's call it an advance, then.
فلنسميها تقدمًا إذن.
You scored an 8 out of 100 on your last test
لقد حصلت على 8 من 100 في اختبارك الأخير
That's a good number.
هذا رقم جيد.
Not so great if it's a test score, though.
ولكن ليس الأمر رائعًا إذا كانت نتيجة اختبار.
Is something wrong?
هل هناك شيء خاطئ؟
Oh, no.
أوه لا.
I was just thinking
كنت أفكر فقط
about the number.
حول الرقم.
Does Uncle Kaishin like the number, too?
هل العم كايشين يحب الرقم أيضًا؟
Uncle Ai has always loved it.
لقد أحبها العم آي دائمًا.
The number 8 symbolizes eternity.
الرقم 8 يرمز إلى الأبدية.
If you turn it on its side, it's the infinity symbol, isn't it?
إذا قلبته على جانبه، فهو رمز اللانهاية، أليس كذلك؟
Sounds just like what a romance novelist would say. So romantic.
يبدو تمامًا كما يقول روائي رومانسي. رومانسي جدًا.
When Ai was a kid
عندما كان آي طفلاً
if he was rating things
إذا كان يقيم الأشياء
he'd always give his favorite things an 8.
كان دائمًا يعطي الأشياء المفضلة لديه علامة 8.
In the toy store, it was "that's an 8, this is an 8".
في متجر الألعاب، كان "هذا هو 8، وهذا هو 8".
Honestly.
بصدق.
He was a kid who always kept us on our toes.
لقد كان طفلاً يبقينا دائمًا على أهبة الاستعداد.
So for Uncle Ai, an 8 means he'll love it forever.
بالنسبة للعم آي، 8 يعني أنه سيحبه إلى الأبد.
My score for Kaishin...
نتيجتي لكايشين...
is an 8.
هو 8.
Out of 100
من أصل 100
isn't a failing grade?
أليس هذا درجة رسوب؟
I just like the number.
أعجبني الرقم فقط.
Uncle Kaishin.
عم كايشين.
I am fine.
أنا بخير.
Where is my bracelet?
أين سوارتي؟
Bracelet? What bracelet?
سوار؟ أي سوار؟
The one that was in the trash.
الذي كان في سلة المهملات.
I already took out the trash.
لقد أخرجت القمامة بالفعل.
Where did you take it?
أين أخذته؟
To the garbage dump.
إلى مكب النفايات.
Unbelievable.
لا يصدق.
It's gone.
لقد ذهب.
Wait.
انتظر.
Hold on.
يتمسك.
You have to love the sea with all your heart.
يجب عليك أن تحب البحر بكل قلبك.
Let's make up.
دعونا نتصالح.
Can I hold you?
هل يمكنني أن أحملك؟
Just let me say one last thing.
دعني أقول شيئاً أخيراً.
I love you.
أحبك.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Kaishin, I'm sorry.
كاشين، أنا آسف.
Please come back.
من فضلك عد مرة أخرى.
Please, just come back.
من فضلك، فقط عد إلى هنا.
I...
أنا...
was so happy being loved by you
لقد كنت سعيدًا جدًا لأنني أحببتك
but I was terrified you'd hate me.
ولكنني كنت خائفة من أنك ستكرهني.
Please come back.
من فضلك عد مرة أخرى.
Please...
لو سمحت...
Do you really want to throw this away?
هل تريد حقا التخلص من هذا؟
- Give it back. - So you can throw it away again?
-أرجعها. -حتى تتمكن من التخلص منها مرة أخرى؟
Give it back to me
أعيدها لي
I'm not giving it back until you answer me.
لن أعيدها لك حتى تجيبني.
I don't know what to do!
لا أعرف ماذا أفعل!
I'm so scared of loving someone.
أنا خائفة جدًا من حب شخص ما.
What can I do...
ماذا يمكنني أن أفعل...
to make him stay by my side
لجعله يبقى بجانبي
the way sister and mom have always been?
كيف كانت الاخت و الام دائما؟
When you're writing a novel
عندما تكتب رواية
are you afraid no one will read it?
هل أنت خائف من أن لا يقرأه أحد؟
No.
لا.
I write because I want to write.
أكتب لأنني أريد أن أكتب.
Exactly!
بالضبط!
You can't be afraid of losing something you haven't lost yet.
لا يمكنك أن تخاف من فقدان شيء لم تفقده بعد.
If you want to love, then love.
إذا كنت تريد أن تحب، فأحب.
Pain, sadness
الألم والحزن
even falling in or out of love
حتى الوقوع في الحب أو الخروج منه
are all just part of the human beings.
كلهم مجرد جزء من البشر.
But...
لكن...
you'll never find happiness if you don't give love.
لن تجد السعادة أبدًا إذا لم تقدم الحب.
You'll never know if it'll lead to happiness or sorrow...
لن تعرف أبدًا ما إذا كان سيؤدي إلى السعادة أم الحزن...
unless you break down the walls around your heart.
إلا إذا حطمت الجدران حول قلبك.
If you don't want to get hurt by losing someone
إذا كنت لا تريد أن تتأذى من فقدان شخص ما
then you just have to cherish them while you can.
إذن عليك فقط أن تعتز بهم بينما تستطيع ذلك.
How am I supposed to do that?
كيف من المفترض أن أفعل ذلك؟
Kaishin made his choice to come here
لقد اتخذ كايشين قراره بالمجيء إلى هنا
now, it's your turn to choose, Ai.
الآن، جاء دورك للاختيار، أي.
As for me,
أما بالنسبة لي،
whatever my friend chooses
مهما اختار صديقي
I'll be right there by his side.
سأكون هناك بجانبه.
I...
أنا...
I want to love someone.
أريد أن أحب شخصًا ما.
And I want to be loved, too.
وأنا أريد أن أكون محبوبًا أيضًا.
And if you get hurt,
وإذا تعرضت للأذى،
we'll be here for you.
سوف نكون هنا من أجلك.
Brother.
أخ.
That last customer...
ذلك العميل الأخير...
already booked their next appointment.
لقد حجزوا بالفعل موعدهم القادم.
Kaishin's back at full power!
كايشين عاد بكامل قوته!
Brother?
أخ؟
Oh, right.
أوه، صحيح.
That's great.
هذا عظيم.
What are you doing back here?
ماذا تفعل هنا في الخلف؟
Huh?
هاه؟
- Isn't you craving me to come back... - Yeah, I know, but...
- هل أنت تتوق إلى عودتي... - نعم، أعلم، ولكن...
if you come back, come back in one piece.
إذا عدت، عد قطعة واحدة.
You look like a complete zombie.
أنت تبدو وكأنك زومبي كامل.
Like you left half of your soul back there.
وكأنك تركت نصف روحك هناك.
Leave me alone.
اتركني وحدي.
Looking at you now,
أنظر إليك الآن،
I guess things didn't work out with that handsome rich guy.
أعتقد أن الأمور لم تنجح مع هذا الرجل الوسيم الغني.
He seemed unapproachable anyway.
لقد بدا وكأنه غير قابل للوصول على أية حال.
When he's hungry.
عندما يكون جائعا.
I bet he's never had to lick salt just to survive.
أراهن أنه لم يضطر أبدًا إلى لعق الملح من أجل البقاء على قيد الحياة.
Don't just assume things.
لا تفترض الأشياء فقط.
You know nothing about him.
أنت لا تعرف عنه شيئا.
I just wanted to help you vent your anger.
أردت فقط أن أساعدك في التنفيس عن غضبك.
Mind your own business.
اهتم بأمورك الخاصة.
But...
لكن...
thanks for watching the shop.
شكرا لمشاهدة المتجر.
Well, yeah...
حسنا، نعم...
I'm your right-hand man, after all.
أنا يدك اليمنى، بعد كل شيء.
Huh?
هاه؟
Rich handsome guy...
رجل غني وسيم...
It's you...
إنه أنت...
the one who stole half my brother's soul...
الذي سرق نصف روح أخي...
Kaishin...
كاشين...
Do you know where Kaishin is?
هل تعرف أين يقع كايشين؟
I don't know!
لا أعرف!
Kaishin!
كاشين!
Fine!
بخير!
Okay, okay, I got it...
حسنًا، حسنًا، لقد حصلت عليه...
He was just out...
لقد كان خارجا للتو...
probably went...
ربما ذهب...
- to that place he's been going to lately... - Thank you.
- إلى ذلك المكان الذي كان يذهب إليه مؤخرًا... - شكرًا لك.
It's a pretty long run from here!
إنها مسافة طويلة جدًا من هنا!
Kaishin!
كاشين!
Ai-san.
أي-سان.
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
Kaishin.
كاشين.
Are you here to hurt me?
هل أنت هنا لتؤذيني؟
What?
ماذا؟
- No... - I told you.
- لا... - قلت لك.
Don't return my heart back.
لا تعيد قلبي .
- You've got it all wrong. - Wrong about what?
- لقد أخطأت في كل شيء. - مخطئ في ماذا؟
My feelings aren't worthless to you.
مشاعري ليست بلا قيمة بالنسبة لك.
Did you come to tell me that you can freely trample on my sincere feelings?
هل أتيت لتخبرني أنك تستطيع أن تدوس بكل حرية على مشاعري الصادقة؟
If you don't care, you should just throw it away.
إذا لم يكن الأمر يهمك، فيجب عليك التخلص منه.
But you're pushing me be the one to do so.
لكنك تدفعني لأكون الشخص الذي يقوم بذلك.
Hey!
يا!
You're the one who said...
أنت من قال...
You don't need love.
لا تحتاج إلى الحب.
You don't want to love anyone.
أنت لا تريد أن تحب أحدا.
Our relationship...
علاقتنا...
was just a contract.
كان مجرد عقد.
It was my fault for forcing my feelings on you.
لقد كان خطئي لأنني فرضت مشاعري عليك.
But I'm telling you
ولكنني أخبرك
no matter how much money you pay
بغض النظر عن مقدار المال الذي تدفعه
you can never go back.
لن تتمكن من العودة أبدًا.
Because feelings are priceless.
لأن المشاعر لا تقدر بثمن.
Go back and find someone else.
ارجع وابحث عن شخص آخر.
You throw it away.
ترميها بعيدا.
Don't make me do it myself.
لا تجعلني أفعل ذلك بنفسي.
My heart...
قلبي...
Wait.
انتظر.
Wait for me, Kaishin!
انتظرني يا كاشين!
Wait!
انتظر!
Please.
لو سمحت.
Just...
فقط...
listen to this.
استمع لهذا.
I'm sorry, Kaishin.
أنا آسف، كاشين.
I hurt you.
لقد جرحتك.
I was selfish.
لقد كنت أنانيًا.
And I was a coward.
وكنت جباناً.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
The words you want to hear...
الكلمات التي تريد سماعها
I couldn't say them to your face.
لم أستطع أن أقولها لك في وجهك.
But with a recording
ولكن مع التسجيل
it's like writing an article
إنه مثل كتابة مقال
I can sort through my thoughts
أستطيع فرز أفكاري
and tell you what's really in my heart.
وأخبرك بما في قلبي حقًا.
The only love I've ever known in my life...
الحب الوحيد الذي عرفته في حياتي...
was filled with pain and endless tears.
كانت مليئة بالألم والدموع التي لا نهاية لها.
That's why I was so scared. I didn't know what to do.
لهذا السبب كنت خائفة جدًا. لم أكن أعرف ماذا أفعل.
That's why I ran away from you
لهذا السبب هربت منك
from your love.
من حبك.
You taught me...
لقد علمتني...
those first fluttering feelings
تلك المشاعر الأولى المتلاطمة
and the happiness...
والسعادة...
I want to wake up next to you in the morning...
أريد أن أستيقظ بجانبك في الصباح...
and fall asleep in your arms at night.
وأنام بين ذراعيك ليلاً.
I want to be able to tell you...
أريد أن أكون قادرا على إخبارك...
"I'm tired"
"أنا متعب"
"I'm hungry."
"أنا جائع."
I want to do things for you, too.
أريد أن أفعل أشياء لك أيضًا.
I want to cry with you...
أريد أن أبكي معك...
and laugh with you.
وأضحك معك.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I'm sorry for falling in love with you.
أنا آسف لأنني وقعت في حبك.
It took me too long to realize it.
لقد استغرق الأمر مني وقتًا طويلاً حتى أدرك ذلك.
I'm so sorry.
أنا آسف جدا.
I love you.
أحبك.
Kaishin...
كاشين...
Yes?
نعم؟
Ai-san.
أي-سان.
Kaishin.
كاشين.
I'm right here.
انا هنا .
Kaishin...
كاشين...
I love you.
أحبك.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I'm sorry for the awful things I said.
أنا آسف على الأشياء الفظيعة التي قلتها.
I'm sorry I hurt you.
أنا آسف لقد أذيتك.
And...
و...
You don't have to apologize anymore.
لا داعي للاعتذار بعد الآن.
Then what should I do?
إذن ماذا يجب أن أفعل؟
I'll do anything.
سأفعل أي شيء.
Tell me.
أخبرني.
How you feel about me?
كيف تشعر تجاهي؟
Right now, to my face.
الآن، أمام وجهي.
I love you.
أحبك.
I love Kaishin.
أنا أحب كاشين.
I've fallen in love with the sea with all my heart.
لقد وقعت في حب البحر بكل قلبي.
It came true.
لقد تحقق ذلك.
I love you, too.
أحبك أيضًا.
From now on, and forever.
من الآن فصاعدا، وإلى الأبد.
I can't just leave this island
لا أستطيع مغادرة هذه الجزيرة
I'll come over during the off-season.
سوف آتي خلال فترة خارج الموسم.
So, that means...
لذا، هذا يعني...
we'll only see each other for half the year?
هل سنرى بعضنا البعض لمدة نصف العام فقط؟
I don't want that.
انا لا أريد ذلك.
But I can't just leave this island.
ولكنني لا أستطيع مغادرة هذه الجزيرة.
This is my life.
هذه هي حياتي.
It's my home.
إنه بيتي.
And there are people here who need me.
وهناك أشخاص هنا يحتاجونني.
Then this is what we'll do.
إذن هذا ما سنفعله.
The rest of the year
بقية العام
I'll come here.
سوف اتي الى هنا
I'm a writer. I can work from anywhere.
أنا كاتب. أستطيع العمل من أي مكان.
Even if there are no med spas here.
حتى لو لم تكن هناك منتجعات طبية هنا.
I want to be with the one I love.
أريد أن أكون مع من أحب.
I've never
انا لم افعل ذلك ابدا
understood myself all this time.
لقد فهمت نفسي طوال هذا الوقت.
He was the one who stripped away my armor
هو الذي نزع عني درعي
filled my naked heart
ملأ قلبي العاري
with overflowing tenderness.
مع الحنان المتدفق.
That's why I can say now.
ولهذا السبب أستطيع أن أقول الآن.
What love means...
ماذا يعني الحب...
is me being together with you
هل أنا معك؟
as it should be.
كما ينبغي أن يكون.
Kaishin.
كاشين.
I'm finally finished.
لقد انتهيت أخيرا.
You must be exhausted.
لا بد أنك مرهق.
Just as I'd expect from you
كما أتوقع منك تمامًا
you are a true genius.
أنت عبقري حقيقي.
Your complement...
مُكملك...
is making me blush.
يجعلني احمر خجلا.
When did you learn the island dialect?
متى تعلمت اللهجة الجزيرة؟
I love you.
أحبك.
Kaishin.
كاشين.
Ai-san.
أي-سان.
Ai-san, are you tired?
أيسان هل أنت متعبة؟
So tired.
متعبة جداً.
I'm wiped.
لقد تم مسحي.
Kaishin.
كاشين.
Yeah?
نعم؟
You have to love, you know.
يجب عليك أن تحب، كما تعلم.
I already do
انا افعل ذلك بالفعل